JESSICA F. VERSOZA

Software Engineer

SUMMARY

Resourceful, full-stack developer with the proven ability to assess and manage complex development obstacles in the software paradigm, and produce excellent results within a set time. Successful in demanding environments, providing decisive problem-solving procedures to address and solve highly challenging problems. With nearly a decade of experience as a respiratory therapist, I am motivated to pursue an exciting professional venture at the intersection of technology and healthcare.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer | 100Devs, Los Angeles, CA

January 2022 — Present

Created full stack web applications and static websites with software developers via high-quality, scalable code.

Recent Projects:

Dimensional Depot (Fullstack Web App) – Add items to your DnD character inventory either by creating your own, or importing items from DnD 5e.

Express Yourself (Fullstack Web App) – Users can login to their profile and find their list of notes. They can add new notes through an input, which they can then edit or delete all notes in their profile.

Software Engineer | Urban Oasis, Sacramento, CA

August 2022 — December 2022

- Collaborated with a team of developers to build modern and responsive web applications using best practices
- Built semantically structured full stack web applications

Respiratory Therapist | Sacramento, CA

April 2021 — June 2023

- Achieved 40% reduction in patient re-testing visits by implementing personalized and precise testing methods, resulting in accurate reports tailored to individual needs.
- -Streamlined lab maintenance and equipment requisition, improving patient delays up to 25%

Respiratory Therapist | Sacramento, CA

March 2017 — Present

- Communicated with a multidisciplinary team clearly and effectively, resulting in rapid response to patients' individual needs.
- Applied critical thinking and creative problem solving to daily tasks, maintaining 100% patient satisfaction

CONTACT

916.995.9874

ifverse@gmail.com

versoza-tech.netlify.app/

https://github.com/ AngerOverApathy

www.linkedin.com/in/iess-vers

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Node

MongoDB

SQL

Express

OOP

Web Accessibility

EDUCATION

UC DAVIS

2021 - 2022

Major: Full-stack Coding

BOISE STATE

2015 - 2017

Major: Bachelors Respiratory Therapy